<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[DarkIntentions] Woohooer</name>
	<author>AliceTries</author>
	<targetVersion>0.19.2009</targetVersion>
	<description>
    Release A2

    Adds Sims (tm) like commands for woohooing with Pawns, including try for baby.


    How this works:
    Adds a new ThoughDef (does not effect JobDef_Loving) and JobGiver (for ui click, requires basic (like flick))
    Pregnancy is already a HeDiff defined for humanlikes; we human likes have a gestation period and the likes as do animals, in humanlikes case the default is 45.
    This is enabled "Woohoo with {Other}" (1% chance (Disabled for A1)) and "Try for Baby {Other}" which has a 50% chance, which can be reduced by Fertility if defined as a capacity.

    Birds and Bees Support by Fluffy
    If Fertility or Reproduction is a defined capacity then it is the average of the two partners then multiplies it times the base chance. To have a baby, each person must be fertile and their must be at least one person with a womb.

    TODO Dice Rolls, Currently always accept and only pregnant when try for baby.

    TODO Mod Settings
    
    Additionally the Woohoo yeilding Babies is integrated with Children and Families mod if you prefer that child generator over random babies from the base game generator.
    
    Release Notes:
    A2 : 
    Major: 
    Integrate with Children and Families, may be loaded above or below; I prefer above to ensure any nonsense in the other mod always overrules
    Minor:
    Check if already pregnant in this rather than in letting the game codes mate do it after we try to make a baby. 
    this allows ui button to not show up if not pregnant.

    (This is the dev version of DarkIntentions. The release version of About.xml is available for editing at About/About-Release.xml. Edits made on this file or on the temporary About/About.xml won't show up on the release version. Use VisualStudio to build a "Release" version of this mod when ready to upload your mod!)</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/AliceTries/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>