<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>[DarkIntentions] Woohooer</name>
    <author>AliceTries</author>
    <targetVersion>0.19.2009</targetVersion>
    <description>
        Release B19, 1.0:

        Adds Sims (tm) like commands for woohooing with Pawns, including try for baby.

        Details:
        This creates context options of "Woohoo with {Other}" and "Try for Baby {Other}" with Colonists and Prisoners

        Please "don't" create a cannibal farm.

        Having a Baby with a prisoner will result in a Baby joining your faction. If the colonist partner is around they may grant amnesty to the mother as well (colonist recruits prisoner).

        Integrations:
        Birds and Bees :
        Uses the Fertility Capabilities if there

        Children School and Families :
        If this mod is enabled will use that child generator over this mods random babies from the base game generator.

        Generic:
        Will Check for Capabilities named Fertility and Reproduction, which can prevent pregancy.

        Warning:
        Psychology mod will mess with this in a way that spams your logs.
        This is because Psychology tries to Start this job without using the work driver just seeing that this joy is a valid type and trying to do in in a gathering space. Yeah psychology is trying to get your pawns to woohoo a table or campfire in a public place.

        TODO:
        Add Settings, note that the base game forces a second dice role on your pawns age group's fertility. Fertility Starts at 14 in base game.

        Release Notes:
        A5:
        Pregnant Prisoners should spawn baby that is also a prisoner. If the other parent is Kind that pawn will be granted amnesty. Children are always given amnesty.


        A4:
        Major:
        Animation and Motes where appropriate.
        Woohooing tables and campfires with Psychology mod is at an end, causes BaseGame log message as we have to catch in pretoils as our workdriver is skipped. This is a bug with psychology. Sorry, all i can do is make it not horrible.
        Minor:
        Bed Theft wont happen if bed has occupents because something alone the lines of "yeah that was awkward for everyone and we agreed not to do that anymore."
        WooHoo Called on Partner as well so they get the right joy.
        Moodlets!

        A3:
        Major:
        Theft of beds (including prisoner beds) for woohooing in that bed. I should add a moodlet on the owners if in line of sight
        Minor:
        No Med Beds
        Allow Male Pregnancy with installed womb (Cost 3 Medicine, Skill level 8)
        Allow prisoners to be impregnated, current default is that they are not a prisoner on spawn but a "free" pawn of the mothers faction. Will need to create a Harmony Patch in A4


        A2 :
        Major:
        Integrate with Children and Families, may be loaded above or below; I prefer above to ensure any nonsense in the other mod always overrules
        Minor:
        Check if already pregnant in this rather than in letting the game codes mate do it after we try to make a baby.
        this allows ui button to not show up if not pregnant.

        ----

        Source is in the public domain, and always available at https://github.com/alycecil/RimworldChildrenWoohoo
    </description>
    <url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/AliceTries/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>